[POLISHED] Hello, welcome to this video tutorial.
[POLISHED] Today we will learn how to use this translation tool.
[POLISHED] First, you need to select your SRT file.
[POLISHED] Then configure your API settings.
[POLISHED] Finally, click the translate button to start.
[POLISHED] The tool will process your file batch by batch.
[POLISHED] You can see the progress in real time.
[POLISHED] The translated file will be saved automatically.
[POLISHED] Thank you for watching this tutorial.
[POLISHED] Please subscribe for more content.
[POLISHED] This tool supports multiple languages including French.
[POLISHED] Vous pouvez traduire en français facilement.